现在在离开此入门部分之前，
Now before leaving this Getting Started section,
让我给你八个快速考虑如何
let me give you eight quick considerations on how to
实际参加这门课程。
actually take this course.
我保证他们是超级短的
And I promise that they are a super short
而且超级重要。
and super important.
所以请，请不要跳过这个视频。
So please, please, don't skip this video.
它将为您在本课程中取得成功做好准备。
It will set you up for success with this course.
所以开始，
So to start,
很有可能这是您的第一次接触
chances are that this is your very first contact
与编写代码。
with writing code.
所以请不要不知所措。
And so please don't get overwhelmed.
我真的看到成千上万的学生去
I have literally seen tens of thousands of students going
通过本课程或我的其他课程之一。
through this course or one of my other courses.
我可以告诉你这是100%正常的
And I can tell you that it's 100% normal,
一开始你不会真正理解
that in the beginning you will not really understand
一切。
everything.
因此，请继续阅读前几节。
So just keep going through these first few sections.
即使你一开始没有百分百了解，
Even if you don't understand 100% at first,
你很快就会的，相信我。
you will very soon, believe me.
这很正常。
That's just normal.
只是不要想像，
Just don't think something like,
我猜编码不适合我。
I guess coding is not for me.
因此，这里根本不允许这种想法。
So that thought is simply not allowed here.
还要记住，每个人都有不同的学习
Also keep in mind that everyone has different learning
速度。
speeds.
所以你最终会到达那里，
And so you will get there eventually,
继续关注课程
just keep following the course
并尽可能多地练习。
and keep practicing as much as you can.
现在关于实际参加课程。
Now about actually taking the course.
你总是，总是需要和我一起编码。
You always, always need to code along with me.
这绝对是根本性的。
And this is absolutely fundamental.
您将通过简单地学习完全零 HTML 和 CSS 技能
You will learn exactly zero HTML and CSS skills by simply
坐在那里看着我写代码。
sitting there and watching me code.
所以你真的必须自己写代码，
So you really have to actually write the code yourself,
即使您只是输入与我完全相同的单词
even if you're just typing the exact same words as I am
基本上是在视频中打字，但这并不重要。
typing basically in a video, but it really doesn't matter.
只要你在编码，
As long as you're coding,
代码正在进入你的大脑，你正在学习。
the code is getting into your brain and you're learning.
所以这才是最重要的。
And so that's all that matters.
如果你想让课程材料留在你的大脑中，
If you want a course material to stick in your brain,
更好的是，然后做笔记。
even better, then take notes.
所以关于代码语法的注释，关于理论概念的注释，
So notes on code syntax, notes on theory concepts,
并真正注意一切。
and really notes on everything.
你不能记太多笔记。
You can't take too many notes.
现在，每个人都有自己的风格。
Now, everyone has their own style.
所以只需要找到你自己的。
So just find your own one.
接下来，尝试我向您展示的所有编码挑战。
Next, try all the coding challenges that I present to you.
尽力做到最好，
Try to do the best that you can,
但如果你因为某种原因卡得太久，
but if you get stuck for too long, for some reason,
继续看解决方案。
just go ahead and watch the solution.
再说一次，
So again,
你必须尝试编码挑战。
you have to try the coding challenges.
否则你会错过很多学习机会
Otherwise you will miss a lot of the learning opportunity
在这里，也不要打败自己
here and also don't beat yourself up
如果你想不出解决办法。
if you can't figure out the solution.
再次，这是完全正常的，
Again, this is completely normal,
特别是如果你只是一个初学者。
especially if you're just a beginner.
相信我。
Trust me.
所以如果发生这种情况只是为了重新观看之前的讲座
So if that happens just to rewatch the lectures that were
在那个挑战中，
covered in that challenge,
试着更好地理解它们，然后继续前进。
try to understand them a bit better and then move on.
现在，课程中的各个部分相互依存。
Now, the sections in the course build on one another.
所以在从一节继续下一节之前，
And so before moving on from a section to the next one,
真的要确保你完全理解是什么
really make sure that you understand exactly what was
该部分涵盖。
covered in that section.
所以休息一下，回顾一下我们写的代码，
So take a break, review the code that we wrote,
查看你的笔记，
review your notes,
并查看我们在那段时间构建的项目化。
and also review the projects that we built in that section.
如果有的话，
If there was any,
你甚至应该尝试提出你自己的例子
you should even try to come up with your own examples and
为了练习，自己写一些代码。
write some code on your own in order to practice.
只有这样你才真正准备好继续前进
And only then you are really ready to move on
到下一节。
to the next section.
现在，如果您的代码有问题或错误，
Now, if you have a question or an error in your code,
总是从尝试自己解决错误开始。
always start by trying to solve the error by yourself.
这对你的进步和你的
This is absolutely essential for your progress and your
学习之旅。
learning journey.
因为开发人员必须做的主要事情之一是
Because one of the main things that a developer has to do is
查找并修复我们也称它们的错误或错误。
to find and fix errors or bugs as we also call them.
现在，如果你能解决问题，
Now, if you can solve the problem,
然后继续查看此处的 Q 和 A 部分
then go ahead and check out the Q and A section here
在 Udemy 上，因为可能是其他人
on Udemy, because probably someone else
之前已经有同样的问题。
already had the same problem before.
如果这也没有帮助，
If that also doesn't help,
那么你当然可以提出一个新问题。
then of course you can ask a new question.
为此，请使用简短描述，
To do that, use a short description,
在 codepen.io 上发布您的代码
post your code on codepen.io
并在问答中分享链接。
and share the link in the Q&amp;A.
所以不要只是在问答中粘贴一堵代码墙，
So don't just paste a wall of code into the Q&amp;A,
但是，请使用 codepen.io 等服务。
but instead, please use a service such as codepen.io.
下一个，
Next,
我只是想快速提一下我录制了这门课程
I just wanted to quickly mention that I recorded this course
在 Mac 上，
on a Mac,
但一切都会以完全相同的方式进行
but everything is going to work the exact same way on
Windows 或 Linux 上。
Windows or on Linux.
因此，如果您的计算机上出现问题，
So if something doesn't work on your computer,
这不是因为您使用的是不同的操作系统。
it's not because you're using a different operating system.
好的。
Okay.
现在终于到手了，你甚至可以说，最重要的是，
And now finally hand, you can say even most importantly,
在做这门课的时候玩得开心。
have fun while doing this course.
编码很有趣，看到它很有意义
Coding is a lot of fun and it's so rewarding to see
你自己建造的东西。
something that you have built yourself.
所以如果你因为某种原因感到沮丧，
So if for some reason you're feeling frustrated,
然后停止你正在做的任何事情，然后再回来。
then just stop whatever you're doing and come back later.
再说一次，
So again,
你总是需要在编码和所有这一切的过程中获得乐趣
you always need to have fun while coding and with all this
话虽如此，让我们现在终于开始了。
being said, let's now finally get started.